Even within the midst of flowing time
流れてく　時の中ででも
Look, indifference still goes round and round
気だるさが　ほらグルグル廻って
As for me, my heart has separated from me
私から　離れる心も
I can't see it, yeah, don't you see?
見えないわ　そう知らない？
Even if I don't move
自分から　動くこともなく
I continue to be lengthened in the cracks of time
時の隙間に　流され続けて
I don't understand what surrounds me
知らないわ　周りのことなど
But I'm still me, and that's it
私は私　それだけ
Am I dreaming? Am I seeing something?
夢見てる？　なにも見てない？
Are all of my words just useless?
語るも無駄な　自分の言葉？
I'm just fed up with being sad
悲しむなんて　疲れるだけよ
"To feel nothing" is the best
何も感じず　過ごせばいいの
Even if I were to speak these confusing words
戸惑う言葉　与えられても
It's just my heart and the sky above me
自分の心　ただ上の空
If I were to move
もし私から　動くのならば
Everything would return and I'd turn it black
すべて変えるのなら　黒にする
Is there future for me?
こんな自分に　未来はあるの？
Do I exist in this world?
こんな世界に　私はいるの？
Am I oppressed? Am I saddened?
今切ないの？　今悲しいの？
I know nothing about me
自分の事も　わからないまま
Even when I'm walking, I'm sick of it
歩むことさえ　疲れるだけよ
So how would I care for other people
人のことなど　知りもしないわ
If a person like me were to change
こんな私も　変われるのなら
If I were to change, I'd turn white
もし変われるのなら　白になる？
Even within the midst of flowing time
流れてく　時の中ででも
Look, indifference still goes round and round
気だるさがほら　グルグル廻って
As for me, my heart is far away from me
私から　離れる心も
I can't see it, don't you see?
見えないわそう　知らない？
Even if I don't move
自分から　動くこともなく
I continue to be lengthened in the cracks of time
時の隙間に　流され続けて
Even if I don't understand what surrounds me
知らないわ　周りのことなど
I am me, and that's it
私は私　それだけ
Am I dreaming? Am I seeing something?
夢見てる？　なにも見てない？
Are all of my words just useless?
語るも無駄な　自分の言葉？
I'm just fed up with being sad
悲しむなんて　疲れるだけよ
"To feel nothing" is best
何も感じず　過ごせばいいの
Even if I were to speak these confusing words
戸惑う言葉　与えられても
It's just my heart and the sky above me
自分の心　ただ上の空
If I were to move
もし私から　動くのならば
Everything would return and I'd turn it black
すべて変えるのなら　黒にする
If I were to move, if I were to move,
動くのならば　動くのならば
Then I'd break everything, I'd break everything
すべて壊すわ　すべて壊すわ
If I were to be sad, if I were to be sad,
悲しむならば　悲しむならば
Would my heart turn white?
私の心　白く変われる？
About you and me
貴方の事も　私のことも
About everything, I don't know a thing
全ての事も　まだ知らないの
If my mental eyelids were to open
重い目蓋を　開けたのならば
If you were to break it just turn black!!!
すべて壊すのなら　黒になれ！！！